Guide to the Robert M. Solow Papers, 1951-2011 and undated RL.01230
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, 1960-2013, 567352; 70 boxes
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1960-2013 and undated, 567400
    - 1980 May.-1980 Aug., 567844 (Box 12)
    - 1980 Sep., 567843 (Box 12)
    - 1980 Oct., 567842 (Box 12)
    - 1980 Nov.-1980 Dec., 567841 (Box 12)
    - 1981 Jan., 567840 (Box 12)
    - 1981 Feb., 567839 (Box 12)
      Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
    - 1981 Mar., 567838 (Box 12)
      Herschel I. Grossman.
    - 1981 Apr., 567837 (Box 12)
      C. Alan Garner
    - 1981 Jun.-1981 Aug., 567836 (Box 12)
      Reply to Edward P. Lazear on labor market.
    - 1981 Sep., 567835 (Box 12)
      Kosta Tsipis.
    - 1981 Oct., 567834 (Box 12)
      Daniel P. Moynihan, U.S. Senate.
    - 1981 Nov., 567833 (Box 13)
      John Kennan, Assar Lindbeck.
    - 1981 Dec., 567832 (Box 13)
      James Tobin, Allen R. Ferguson.
    - 1982 Jan., 567831 (Box 13)
      Gunnar Tomasson, Hans T. Soderstrom.
    - 1982 Feb.-1982 Mar., 567830 (Box 13)
      Correspondence with Ronald Coase on methodology, Michael Hoel.
    - 1982 Mar., 567829 (Box 13)
      Don Patinkin, Alan S. Blinder. A draft of "A Curmudgeonely Note on the New Econometrics."
    - 1982 Apr., 567828 (Box 13)
    - 1982 May, 567827 (Box 13)
      Gary Hart, Don Patinkin.
    - 1982 Jun.-1982 Jul., 567826 (Box 13)
      James A. Mireless, N. Gregory Mankiw, correspondence with Yoram Barzel on price formation process.
    - 1982 Sep.-1982 Oct., 567825 (Box 14)
      George Akerlof, Robert E. Hall.
    - 1982 Nov.-1982 Dec., 567824 (Box 14)
    - 1983 Jan., 567823 (Box 14)
      Robert W. Clower.
    - 1983 Jan.-1983 Feb., 567822 (Box 14)
      Partha Dasgupta, Frenk Hahn, John Hicks, Robert Merton.
    - 1983 Mar., 567821 (Box 14)
    - 1983 Apr.- 1983 May, 567820 (Box 14)
      Ian M. McDonald, Thomas E. Anger, John Kennan.
    - 1983 May.- 1983 Jun., 567819 (Box 14)
      Sven Herner, David Halzman, Edward Lazear, Frank H. Hahn.
    - 1983 Jul.- 1983 Sep., 567818 (Box 14)
      Donald M. McCloskey. Correspondence with Frank Hahn on rational expectations.
    - 1983 Oct.- 1983 Dec., 567817 (Box 15)
    - 1983 Dec., 567816 (Box 15)
      Tapan Biswas.
    - 1984 Jan., 567815 (Box 15)
      Correspondence with Philip Cagan and his draft "Anticipated and Unanticipated Changes in Wealth and the Consumption Function.". Referee report on Meltzer's outline of a book on Keynes.
    - 1984 Feb.- 1984 Apr., 567814 (Box 15)
      Mo-huan Hsing.
    - 1984 May- 1984 Jul., 567813 (Box 15)
    - 1984 Jul.- 1984 Aug., 567812 (Box 15)
      Memorandum of "Economic Trends Pointing to the Importance of Ocean Resources".
    - 1984 Sep., 567811 (Box 15)
      Herbert Gintis.
    - 1984 Oct., 567810 (Box 15)
      Donald McCloskey, Andrew J. Oswald, Moses Abramovitz.
    - 1984 Nov., 567809 (Box 15)
      George Akerloff, Alan Blinder, James K. Galbraith, Herbert A. Simon, George Stigler.
    - 1984 Dec., 567808 (Box 16)
      Peter Sinclair.
    - 1985 Jan., 567807; 1 of 2 (Box 16)
    - 1985 Jan., 567806; 2 of 2 (Box 16)
      Virginia Dominguez, Frank H Hahn.
    - 1985 Feb., 567805 (Box 16)
      Short correspondence.
    - 1985 Mar., 567804 (Box 16)
      Patricia Williams, Geoffrey Hall.
    - 1985 Apr., 567803 (Box 16)
    - 1985 May.-1985 Sep., 567802 (Box 16)
      Daniel Bell, Donald McCloskey.
    - 1985 Oct., 567801; 1 of 2 (Box 16)
      Donald McCloskey, Richard H. Thaler. Report on Axel Leijonhufvud.
    - 1985 Oct., 567800; 2 of 2 (Box 16)
      Manuscript "Population Growth and Economic Development: Policy Questions." by National Research Council.
    - 1985 Nov., 567799 (Box 17)
      Milton Friedman, Stanley Fischer.
    - 1985 Dec., 567798 (Box 17)
      Martha C. Nussbaum.
    - 1986 Jan., 567797; 1 of 2 (Box 17)
      Walter W. Heller.
    - 1986 Jan., 567796; 2 of 2 (Box 17)
      Heidi I. Hartmann.
    - 1986 Feb., 567795 (Box 17)
      Nicholas Oulton on bargaining, James J. Heckman.
    - 1986 Mar., 567794 (Box 17)
      Franco Modigliani, Paul Samuelson, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
    - 1986 Apr., 567793 (Box 17)
      Andrew J. Oswald, Paul A. David.
    - 1986 May, 567792 (Box 17)
      Mortimer Appley, Akira Takayama.
    - 1986 Jun.-1986 Aug., 567791 (Box 17)
      David A. Colander, Avinash Dixit.
    - 1986 Sep., 567790 (Box 18)
      Peter Diamond, Hiroshi Yoshikawa.
    - 1986 Oct., 567789; 1 of 2 (Box 18)
      John E. Cremeans.
    - 1986 Oct., 567788; 2 of 2 (Box 18)
      A report to the Committee on the operation of Economics program by Oversight Committee, Kenneth J. Arrow, Claudia Goldin, Dale W. Jorgenson, Robert E. Lucas, Veron Smith, Robert M. Solow, Joseph E. Stiglitz.
    - 1986 Nov., 567787; 1 of 2 (Box 18)
      Referee report on Julian L. Simon's manuscript "The Perverseness of Hotelling's Rule." Correspondence about the manuscript "Keynes, Lucas, and Scientific Revolutions." by Alan Blinder. Manuscript by David Colander "In Defense of Mainstream Economics."
    - 1986 Nov., 567786; 2 of 2 (Box 18)
      Alan Abouchar.
    - 1986 Dec., 567785 (Box 18)
      Roy Weintraub.
    - 1987 Jan., 567784 (Box 18)
      K. Velupillai, W.M. Gorman, a manuscript titled "Economists, Politcs and Chance".
    - 1987 Feb., 567783 (Box 18)
      Assar Lindbeck. Correspondence with Herbert A. Simon about his manuscript "Some Trivial but Useful Mathematics: Ordinal Variables." Correspondence with U.S. Senators: Lawton Chiles, P.V. Domenici, J. Bennett Johnston.
    - 1987 Mar., 567782 (Box 18)
      Matthew Shapiro.
    - 1987 Apr., 567781 (Box 18)
      Joseph E. Stiglitz, Robert Eisner.
    - 1987 May., 567780 (Box 19)
      Don Patinkin, Andrew Oswald, David J. Smyth, Arjo Klamer.
    - 1987 Jun.-1987 Aug., 567779 (Box 19)
    - 1987 Sep., 567778 (Box 19)
      Partha Dasgupta, RObert W. Fogel.
    - 1987 Oct., 567777 (Box 19)
      Harvey Leibenstein. Letters congratilating to the Nobel Prize award.
    - 1987 Nov., 567776; 1 of 2 (Box 19)
      Letters congratilating to the Nobel Prize award.
    - 1987 Nov., 567775; 2 of 2 (Box 19)
      Myron J. Gordon.
    - 1987 Dec., 567774; 1 of 2 (Box 19)
      Assar Lindbeck, Orley Ashenfelter.
    - 1987 Dec., 567773; 2 of 2 (Box 19)
      Heidi Hartmann, Herschel Grossman.
    - 1988 Jan., 567772; 1 of 2 (Box 20)
      Alfred P. Sloan Foundation. A letter of recommendation for Amartya Sen.
    - 1988 Jan., 567771; 2 of 2 (Box 20)
      Dale W. Jorgenson.
    - 1988 Feb., 567770; 1 of 2 (Box 20)
      John B. Slaughter, William J. Baumol.
    - 1988 Feb., 567769; 2 of 2 (Box 20)
      Avi J. Cohen.
    - 1988 Mar., 567768; 1 of 2 (Box 20)
      Lester O. Bumas.
    - 1988 Mar., 567767; 2 of 2 (Box 20)
      Robert U. Ayres.
    - 1988 Apr., 567766; 1 of 2 (Box 20)
      Frank Hahn, Andrew Clark.
    - 1988 Apr., 567765; 2 of 2 (Box 21)
      Arthur L. Singer Jr., Gunnar Tomasson.
    - 1988 May., 567764; 1 of 2 (Box 21)
      A reply to John R. Garrett's review of Sargent, Nancy Folbre, Jorgen Weibull.
    - 1988 May., 567763; 2 of 2 (Box 21)
      Kenneth J. Arrow.
    - 1988 Jun., 567762 (Box 21)
      David Robinson, Pekka Tiainen, George J. Stigler.
    - 1988 Jul-1988 Aug., 567761 (Box 21)
      M.A.H. Dempster.
    - 1988 Sep., 567760 (Box 21)
      Newell D. Sanders, Harold G. Vatter.
    - 1988 Oct., 567759 (Box 21)
    - 1988 Nov., 567758; 1 of 2 (Box 21)
      Burton H. Klein.
    - 1988 Nov., 567757; 2 of 2 (Box 22)
    - 1988 Dec., 567756 (Box 22)
      Robert Heilbroner, Richard Stone, Burton H. Klein, Daniel Bell, a reply to Assar Lindbeck regarding the Nobel Prize nominations.
    - 1989 Jan., 567755; 1 of 2 (Box 22)
      Jack Repcheck, Robert H. Haveman.
    - 1989 Jan., 567754; 2 of 2 (Box 22)
      A reply from Assar Linbeck regarding the Nobel Prize nominations.
    - 1989 Feb., 567753 (Box 22)
      Franco Modigliani, a draft report to the executive committee of the AEA Ad Hoc Committee on the Journal of Economic Perspectives by Leonid Hurwicz, Michael S. McPherson, Albert Rees, Robert M. Solow, William J. Baumol.
    - 1989 Mar., 567752; 1 of 3 (Box 22)
      Julian L. Simon, John DeSaix.
    - 1989 Mar., 567751; 2 of 3 (Box 22)
      Martin Feldstein, Timothy J. Kehoe, David Landes, J.A. Mirrlees. Correspondence with D.P. Moynihan, U.S. Senate.
    - 1989 Mar., 567750; 3 of 3 (Box 22)
    - 1989 Apr., 567749; 1 of 2 (Box 23)
    - 1989 Apr., 567748; 2 of 2 (Box 23)
      Samuel Bowles.
    - 1989 May, 567747; 1 of 2 (Box 23)
      Lloyd Ulman.
    - 1989 May, 567746; 2 of 2 (Box 23)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, Priscilla K. Gray. Letter to Julius Margolis on T. Schelling
    - 1989 Jun., 567745; 1 of 2 (Box 23)
    - 1989 Jun., 567744; 2 of 2 (Box 23)
      Stephen Paley, Richard Goodwin.
    - 1989 Aug., 567743 (Box 23)
    - 1989 Sep., 567742 (Box 23)
      Egon P. Winter, Partha Dasgupta.
    - 1989 Oct., 567741; 1 of 2 (Box 24)
      Peter L. Swan, Martin F. J. Prachowny,Partha Dasgupta, Mujid S. Kazimi.
    - 1989 Oct., 567740; 2 of 2 (Box 24)
      Letter supporting tenure of David Romer.
    - 1989 Dec., 567739; 1 of 2 (Box 24)
    - 1989 Dec., 567738; 2 of 2 (Box 24)
    - 1990 Jan., 567737; 1 of 2 (Box 24)
      Some brochures.
    - 1990 Jan., 567736; 2 of 2 (Box 24)
      D.P. Maynihan, U.S. Senate. Nomination of Paul Samuelson for the National Medal of Science.
    - 1990 Feb., 567735; 1 of 2 (Box 24)
      Gottfried Bombach.
    - 1990 Feb., 567734; 2 of 2 (Box 24)
    - 1990 Mar., 567733; 1 of 2 (Box 25)
      Steven Herzenverg.
    - 1990 Mar., 567732; 2 of 2 (Box 25)
      Mancur Olson, E.S. Phelps.
    - 1990 Apr., 567731 (Box 25)
      Correspondence with Don Patinkin on Keynes, James H. Gupinski.
    - 1990 May., 567730; 1 of 2 (Box 25)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, Ddale W. Jorgenson, Gregory Mankiw, Thomas C. Shelling. Daniel P. Moynihan, U.S. Senate.
    - 1990 May., 567729; 2 of 2 (Box 25)
      Frank H. Hahn, Richard M. Goodwin.
    - 1990 Jun., 567728 (Box 25)
    - 1990 Jul., 567727 (Box 25)
      A reply to Craufurd D. Goodwin on Adam Smith.
    - 1990 Sep., 567726 (Box 25)
      Arthur L. Singer Jr..
    - 1990 Oct., 567725; 1 of 2 (Box 26)
      Ian McDonald.
    - 1990 Oct., 567724; 2 of 2 (Box 26)
      Walter S. Salant, Robert W. Fogel.
    - 1990 Nov., 567723; 1 of 2 (Box 26)
      Report on Donald McCloskey. Open letter to Mikhail Gorbachev, signed by a number of economists. James J. Heckman.
    - 1990 Nov., 567722; 2 of 2 (Box 26)
      Robert W. Fogel, Oliver Williamson, a letter to James J. Heckman on his paper on the labor market equilibrium.
    - 1990 Dec., 567721 (Box 25)
      Gregory C. Chow on capital and growth, Frank H. Hahn, Gottfried Bombach, Ian McDonald.
    - 1991 Jan., 567720; 1 of 2 (Box 26)
      Letter to David Colander on AS-AD model. Letter to Assar Lindbeck on the contributions of Robert Lucas.
    - 1991 Jan., 567719; 2 of 2 (Box 26)
      David Z. Robinson.
    - 1991 Feb., 567718 (Box 27)
      Carolyn Bell.
    - 1991 Mar., 567717 (Box 27)
      Noam Chomsky, Albert Hirschman, Charles R. Plott. Assessment letter about Amartya Sen.
    - 1991 Apr., 567716; 1 of 2 (Box 27)
      P.J.N. Sinclair, correspondence with Christopher Chase-Dunn on the development of macroeconomics.
    - 1991 Apr., 567715; 2 of 2 (Box 27)
      Louis C. Ianniello.
    - 1991 May, 567714 (Box 27)
      Assessment letter about Janet Yellen.
    - 1991 Jun., 567713 (Box 27)
      Nan Friedlaender.
    - 1991 Jul., 567712 (Box 27)
    - 1991 Aug., 567711 (Box 27)
      Letter to D.R. Rusfeld on non-mainstream schools of economics.
    - 1991 Sep., 567710 (Box 27)
      Kenneth G. Elzinga, Arthur L. Singer Jr., Nicholas Oulton.
    - 1991 Oct., 567709; 1 of 3 (Box 28)
      Kevin M. Murphy, Robert H. Topel.
    - 1991 Oct., 567708; 2 of 3 (Box 28)
      Arthur L. Singer Jr.
    - 1991 Oct., 567707; 3 of 3 (Box 28)
      Comments on Ferber-Nelson Volume.
    - 1991 Nov., 567706; 1 of 3 (Box 28)
      Christopher Goerges.
    - 1991 Nov., 567705; 2 of 3 (Box 28)
      Morris Adelman, a reply to J.J. Pollak on capital market.
    - 1991 Nov., 567704; 3 of 3 (Box 28)
      Francis M. Bator.
    - 1991 Dec., 567703 (Box 27)
      Warren Young, Partha Dasgupta, Robert Eisner.
    - 1992 Jan., 567702; 1 of 2 (Box 28)
      Frank H. Hahn, W.W. Rostow, Vernon Smith. Draft of Frank H. Hahn's "Incomplete Market Economies".
    - 1992 Jan., 567701; 2 of 2 (Box 28)
    - 1992 Feb., 567700; 1 of 2 (Box 29)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, W.W. Rostow.
    - 1992 Feb., 567699; 2 of 2 (Box 29)
      D.P. Moynihan, U.S. Senate. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation. James Tobin, statement on U.S. economic policy.
    - 1992 Mar., 567698; 1 of 2 (Box 29)
      Luigi Pasinetti, Arthur L. Singer Jr..
    - 1992 Mar., 567697; 2 of 2 (Box 29)
      Gordon S. G. Beveridge, Russell E. Davis.
    - 1992 Apr., 567696; 1 of 2 (Box 29)
      Mancur Olson, Tibor Scitovski, James Tobin. Joseph R. Biden, U.S. Senate. Franjo Tudman, president of the Republic of Croatia.
    - 1992 Apr., 567695; 2 of 2 (Box 29)
      James Tobin, a reply to Susan Lee on Keynesianism.
    - 1992 May, 567694 (Box 29)
      A reply to Richard P. Nathan on infrastructure investment, William G. Bowen.
    - 1992 Jun., 567693 (Box 29)
      Alan S. Blinder, Robert Feenstra, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, James Tobin.
    - 1992 Jul., 567692; 1 of 2 (Box 30)
      James Tobin, Lawrence R. Klein, Lawrence H. Summers.
    - 1992 Jul., 567691; 2 of 2 (Box 30)
    - 1992 Aug., 567690 (Box 30)
      Orley Ashenfelter, Vernon L. Smith.
    - 1992 Oct., 567689; 1 of 2 (Box 30)
      A reply to Andrea Beltratti on endogenous growth with fixed factors, Gary S. Becker.
    - 1992 Oct., 567688; 2 of 2 (Box 30)
      Donald N. McCloskey.
    - 1992 Nov., 567687; 1 of 3 (Box 30)
      Richard Nelson.
    - 1992 Nov., 567686; 2 of 3 (Box 30)
      Edward C. Prescott, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
    - 1992 Nov., 567685; 3 of 3 (Box 31)
      Steven G. Gallagher,a reply to John S. Atlee on the Clinton Administration and the U.S. economy, Robert Eisner.
    - 1992 Dec., 567684; 1 of 3 (Box 31)
      Luigi Pasinetti.
    - 1992 Dec., 567683; 2 of 3 (Box 31)
      Luigi Pasinetti, J. Ramus, Harry Bernstein on the U.S. economy.
    - 1992 Dec., 567682; 3 of 3 (Box 31)
    - 1993 Jan., 567681 (Box 31)
    - 1993 Feb., 567680; 1 of 2 (Box 31)
      Herbert A. Simon.
    - 1993 Feb., 567679; 2 of 2 (Box 31)
      Susan E. Madori, Paul Davidson.
    - 1993 Mar., 567678; 1 of 4 (Box 31)
      Dale W. Jorgenson, John Quigley.
    - 1993 Mar., 567677; 2 of 4 (Box 31)
      Geoffrey Heal.
    - 1993 Mar., 567676; 3 of 4 (Box 32)
      Daniel Bell.
    - 1993 Mar., 567675; 4 of 4 (Box 32)
      William E. Stoneman, Hajime Hori.
    - 1993 Apr., 567674; 1 of 2 (Box 32)
      Gilles Saint-Paul, Madeline Sunley on proposal for a new journal "Technology, Business and Enviornment", Luigi Pasinetti, Lawrence Katz.
    - 1993 Apr., 567673; 2 of 2 (Box 32)
    - 1993 May, 567672; 1 of 2 (Box 32)
      A manuscript on the U.S. economy.
    - 1993 May, 567671; 2 of 2 (Box 32)
      William D. Nordhaus, Seppo Hankapohja.
    - 1993 Jun., 567670 (Box 32)
      A letter to David Gale from Paul A. Samuelson on the Solow model, Paul M. Sweezy.
    - 1993 Jul., 567669; 1 of 2 (Box 32)
      Responses to Questions for ERGO 2 Newsletter, Paul M. Sweezy.
    - 1993 Jul., 567668; 2 of 2 (Box 32)
      Olivier Blanchard, Kevin Frisch.
    - 1993 Aug., 567667; 1 of 3 (Box 33)
      Paul M. Sweezy, Robert W. Clower.
    - 1993 Aug., 567666; 2 of 3 (Box 33)
      Graciela Chichilnisky.
    - 1993 Aug., 567665; 3 of 3 (Box 33)
      Guy H. Orcutt, Robert W. Clower.
    - 1993 Sep., 567664; 1 of 2 (Box 33)
      Avinash Dixit.
    - 1993 Sep., 567663; 2 of 2 (Box 33)
    - 1993 Oct., 567662; 1 of 3 (Box 33)
      Franco Modigliani, Paul M. Sweezy.
    - 1993 Oct., 567661; 2 of 3 (Box 33)
      Frank Levy.
    - 1993 Oct., 567660; 3 of 3 (Box 33)
      Barney Frank, Edward Kennedy, Gerry Stups.
    - 1993 Nov., 567659; 1 of 3 (Box 33)
      F. Giavazzi, Charles A. Myers.
    - 1993 Nov., 567658; 2 of 3 (Box 33)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, Stephen M. Stigler, Stanley Fisher. Wilson-Friedman correspondence.
    - 1993 Nov., 567657; 3 of 3 (Box 34)
      A letter to Gary S. Becker in memory of George J. Stigler.
    - 1993 Dec., 567656; 1 of 4 (Box 34)
      Paul Romer.
    - 1993 Dec., 567655; 2 of 4 (Box 34)
      Marc Nerlove, Agostino Manduchi.
    - 1993 Dec., 567654; 3 of 4 (Box 34)
      An open letter to prime minister Hosokawa and President Clinton,Jagdish Bhagwati.
    - 1993 Dec., 567653; 4 of 4 (Box 34)
      Martin Hellwig.
    - 1994 Jan., 567652; 1 of 2 (Box 34)
    - 1994 Jan., 567651; 2 of 2 (Box 34)
      Edward Renshaw.
    - 1994 Feb., 567650; 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      James Heckman.
    - 1994 Feb., 567649; 2 of 3 (Box 34)
      A reply to Martin F.J. Prachowny on his paper on the labor market, Edmund S. Phelps.
    - 1994 Feb., 567648; 3 of 3 (Box 35)
    - 1994 Mar., 567647; 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      Edward Renshaw, Zvi Grilliches, Chauncey Starr.
    - 1994 Mar., 567646; 2 of 3 (Box 35)
      Gottfried Bombach, Zui Grilches, Robert W. Fogel.
    - 1994 Mar., 567645; 3 of 3 (Box 35)
    - 1994 Apr., 567644; 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      Roger Koppl, Perry Mehrling.
    - 1994 Apr., 567643; 2 of 3 (Box 35)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, John Conlisk.
    - 1994 Apr., 567642; 3 of 3 (Box 35)
    - 1994 May, 567641; 1 of 2 (Box 35)
      Janos Kornai.
    - 1994 May, 567640; 2 of 2 (Box 35)
      Roger Koppl.
    - 1994 Jun., 567639; 1 of 2 (Box 36)
      Frank H. Hahn, Tibor Scitovsky.
    - 1994 Jun., 567638; 2 of 2 (Box 36)
      Jagdish Bhagwati.
    - 1994 Jul., 567637; 1 of 2 (Box 36)
      John Pezzey, correspondence with John Conlisk on bounded rationality.
    - 1994 Jul., 567636; 2 of 2 (Box 36)
      Kenneth J. Arrow, Edward M. Kennedy, Sumner M. Rosen. Correspondence with Janet Fisher on taking over Review of Economics and Statistics. Janos Kornai's critique of Vaclav Klaus.
    - 1994 Aug., 567635; 1 of 3 (Box 36)
      B.J. Phillips, Harold Hochman.
    - 1994 Aug., 567634; 2 of 3 (Box 36)
      A manuscript on "Social and Economic Issues in Global Sustainability", Olivier Blanchard.
    - 1994 Aug., 567633; 3 of 3 (Box 36)
      Kenneth J. Arrow, Janos Kornai, Sumner M. Rosen, Vernon Smith.
    - 1994 Sep., 567632 (Box 37)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, Tibor Scitovski, Thomas Sowell. Essay "Introduction of William Julius Wilson."
    - 1994 Oct., 567631; 1 of 2 (Box 37)
    - 1994 Oct., 567630; 2 of 2 (Box 37)
      Janas Timar, Peter Gottschalk.
    - 1994 Nov., 567629; 1 of 3 (Box 37)
      Robert Eisner.
    - 1994 Nov., 567628; 2 of 3 (Box 37)
      Avinash Dixit, Frank H. Hahn, Michael Woodford.
    - 1994 Nov., 567627; 3 of 3 (Box 37)
      Jeffrey Kling, Jeremy J. Stone, Robert Dorfman, Jean Tirole.
    - 1994 Dec., 567626; 1 of 2 (Box 37)
      Edward Renshaw, William Lewis.
    - 1994 Dec., 567625; 2 of 2 (Box 37)
      William D. Nordhaus, Sumner M. Rosen.
    - 1995 Jan., 567624; 1 of 2 (Box 38)
    - 1995 Jan., 567623; 2 of 2 (Box 38)
      Albert Carnesale, Partha Dasgupta, Saunders MacLane.
    - 1995 Feb., 567622; 1 of 3 (Box 38)
    - 1995 Feb., 567621; 2 of 3 (Box 38)
      Lonnie R. Sherrod, Alessandro Sderci.
    - 1995 Feb., 567620; 3 of 3 (Box 38)
      Axel Leijonhufvud, Martin Weitzman.
    - 1995 Mar., 567619; 1 of 2 (Box 38)
      A reply to Robin Morris on growth slowdown.
    - 1995 Mar., 567618 (Box 38)
      Olivier Blanchard.
    - 1995 Apr., 567617; 1 of 2 (Box 38)
      F.H. Hahn, Charles M. Plotz. Partha Dasgupta on Nobel Prize nominations.
    - 1995 Apr., 567616; 2 of 2 (Box 39)
      Walter Korpi, Robert W. Fogel.
    - 1995 May, 567615; 1 of 2 (Box 39)
      Robert Eisner, Joseph E. Stiglitz.
    - 1995 May, 567614; 2 of 2 (Box 39)
      A manuscript titled "Notes on the Nickel Problem", Kenneth R. Fulton.
    - 1995 Jun., 567613; 1 of 2 (Box 39)
      Robert Eisner, Robert Kuttner. A letter of Norgarat to Arrow on the system of national accounts. Robert Dorfman on Boehm-Bawerk.
    - 1995 Jun., 567612; 2 of 2 (Box 39)
      Anne O. Krueger, Richard Lester.
    - 1994 Jul., 567611 (Box 39)
    - 1995 Aug., 567610; 1 of 2 (Box 39)
      James Buchanan, Ronald McKinnon, William F Schreiber. Assar Lindbeck on endogenous habits and norms and welfare state. The President of Germany.
    - 1995 Aug., 567609; 2 of 2 (Box 39)
      Ralph E. Gomory,Jagdish Bhagwati, Anne O. Krueger.
    - 1995 Sep., 567608; 1 of 2 (Box 40)
      Kenneth R. Fulton, Charles Plott, Thomas Bender, comments on Peter Diamond's paper on money illusion.
    - 1995 Sep., 567607; 2 of 2 (Box 40)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, Partha Dasgupta, Christina Romer, Ian McDonald. Letter to Ann Sochi on Don Patinkin. Assessment of Perry Mehrling.
    - 1995 Oct., 567606; 1 of 2 (Box 40)
      Michel Baranger.
    - 1995 Oct., 567605; 2 of 2 (Box 40)
      Correspondence with Christoph Klingen on endogenous growth theory.
    - 1995 Nov., 567604; 1 of 2 (Box 40)
      Martin Eichenbaum, David M. Kreps, Paul Krugman.
    - 1995 Dec., 567603; 2 of 2 (Box 40)
    - 1996 Jan., 567602 (Box 41)
      Letter to Ajit Singh on popular disagreement with inflation and overextended welfare state. Letter to Martin Eichenbaum about identification of demand shocks.
    - 1996 Feb., 567601 (Box 41)
      Albert Hirschman, Axel Leijonhufvud. D.P. Moynihan, U.S. Senate.
    - 1996 Mar., 567600; 1 of 3 (Box 41)
      Jagdish Bhagwati. Letter to Laurence Ball on disinflation and NAIRU. Evaluation of Xavier Sala-i-Martin. Letter to Mark Wrighton on NYU.
    - 1996 Mar., 567599; 2 of 3 (Box 41)
      Jagdish Bhagwati. Letter to Karl Schell on learning by doing.
    - 1996 Mar., 567598; 3 of 3 (Box 41)
    - 1996 Apr., 567597; 1 of 2 (Box 41)
      F.H. Hahn. Letter to Martin N. Bailey on a paper on labor productivity.
    - 1996 Apr., 567596; 2 of 2 (Box 41)
    - 1996 May, 567595; 1 of 2 (Box 41)
      Robert A. Levine.
    - 1996 May, 567594; 2 of 2 (Box 41)
      Letter to Lord Desay on scepticism about EMU.
    - 1996 Jun., 567593; 1 of 2 (Box 42)
      Robert Eisner, John E. Tilton, correspondence with Olivier Blanchard on his paper on the natural rate of unemployment.
    - 1996 Jun., 567592; 2 of 2 (Box 42)
      Robert Litan.
    - 1996 Jul., 567591; 1 of 2 (Box 42)
      A letter to William J. Clinton on the welfare reform bill, Robert J. Gordon.
    - 1996 Jul., 567590; 2 of 2 (Box 42)
      Robert E. Rowthorn, Olivier Blanchard.
    - 1996 Aug., 567589 (Box 42)
      Robert J. Gordon on NAIRU.
    - 1996 Sep., 567588; 1 of 2 (Box 42)
      Stephen M. Stigler.
    - 1996 Sep., 567587; 2 of 2 (Box 42)
    - 1996 Oct., 567586 (Box 42)
    - 1996 Nov., 567585; 1 of 3 (Box 42)
      Gregory Chow.
    - 1996 Nov., 567584; 2 of 3 (Box 43)
      James K. Galbraith.
    - 1996 Nov., 567583; 3 of 3 (Box 43)
      A reply to Wynne Godley on Macroeconomic models.
    - 1996 Dec., 567582; 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      Deepak Sinha.
    - 1996 Dec., 567581; 2 of 3 (Box 43)
      Andrei Shleifer, Jagdish Bhagwati on TFP growth.
    - 1996 Dec., 567580; 3 of 3 (Box 43)
    - 1997 Jan., 567579 (Box 43)
      Robert A. Pollak.
    - 1997 Feb., 567578; 1 of 2 (Box 43)
      Luigi Pasinetti, a reply to Marvin Frankel on the AK model.
    - 1997 Feb., 567577; 2 of 2 (Box 43)
      Short papers.
    - 1997 Mar., 567576 (Box 43)
      Herbert Giersch, Geoffrey Heal.
    - 1997 Apr., 567575 (Box 44)
      Heinz Family Foundation - The Heinz Awards. Correspondence with Robert Leeson on personal relationship with George Stigler.
    - 1997 May., 567574; 1 of 2 (Box 44)
      George E. Brown, Jr..
    - 1997 May., 567573; 2 of 2 (Box 44)
      A reply to Assar Lindbeck on new Keynesian movement, Olivier Blanchard.
    - 1997 Jun., 567572 (Box 44)
    - 1997 Jul., 567571; 1 of 2 (Box 44)
      David Barker, Partha Dasgupta.